Finding Aid for Law School (University of Michigan), 1852-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Deans of the Law School, 1852-1999
  - Deans' Files, 1852-1975
    - Regents Communications, Reports, and Petitions, 1852-1962
      Regents Communication, Reports, and Petitions (0.5 linear feet, 1852-1962) is comprised of two files: Regents Communication, and Reports and Petitions. Regents Communication consists of a chronologically arranged file of the Law School's communications to the Regents from 1910 to 1962. The Reports and Petitions, 1852-1924 (scattered dates), although fragmentary in terms of coverage, contains some of the oldest material in the record group, including some documents that predate the School's founding. One, written in 1852, is a petition from 50 citizens requesting the university to establish a law school. Other documents include a report from 1859 outlining the proposed law department, and an 1862 contract for the construction of a law building.
      - Regents Communication, 1910-1962; 3 folders (Box 59)
      - Reports and Petitions, 1852-1924
        - Petition to Establish Law Professorships, 1852 (Box 59)
        - Outline of Proposed Law Department, 1859 (Box 59)
        - Agreements for Erection of Law Building and Desks, 1862-1863 (Box 59)
        - Student Petition Regarding $10 diploma Fee, 1878 (Box 59)
        - Report and Exhibits of Charges Against Law Professors, 1879 (Box 59)
        - Report on Resignation of Professor Thomas M. Cooley, undated (Box 59)
        - Report on Bad Conditions of Water Closets, 1910 (Box 59)
        - Five-Year Need Plan for Law School, 1924 (Box 59)
  - Francis Allen
    The Francis Allen subseries consists of communications between the dean and the faculty, a letter to students, dated March, 14, 1968 regarding the military draft, and a survey of outside employment and other professional service.
    - Communications between Dean and Faculty, 1966-1970; 13 folders (Box 81)
    - Letter to Students regarding Draft, March 14, 1968 (Box 81)
    - Survey--Outside Employment and Other Outside Professional Service, 1970 (Box 81)
  - Deanship Search Committee Files
    The series Deanship Search Committee Files contain records of the 1986-1987 search resulting in the selection of Lee Bollinger as Dean. In 1994, the search files relating to the selection of Jeffrey S. Lehman were added to the record group. Access to the search files is restricted in accordance with applicable laws.
    - Search Files, 1986-1987; 18 folders (Box 73)
      [PR RESTRICTED until 2017 ]
    - Search Files, 1993-1994; 3 folders (Box 75)
      [PR RESTRICTED until 2024 ]
  - Course Evaluations
    The Course Evaluations subseries consists of evaluations compiled by the Law School Student Senate covering the years 1971-1979.
    - Undated (Box 74)
    - 1971 (Box 74)
    - 1972 (Box 74)
    - 1973 (Box 74)
    - 1975 (Box 74)
    - 1976 (Box 74)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 74)
    - 1979 (Box 74)
  - Theodore St. Antoine
    St. Antoine's Dean's Files subseries consists of seven sub-subseries: two alphabetical files covering 1971-1973, and 1973-1975; two chronological file, Pre-deanship Correspondence 1965-1971 and Deanship Correspondence, 1972-1978; Faculty Correspondence, Topical Correspondence and Miscellaneous Correspondence. There are names which are found in both the Faculty Correspondence and the Miscellaneous Correspondence; the correspondence found in the Miscellaneous sub-subseries pertains to these faculty members' administrative duties, while that found in the Faculty sub-subseries pertains to their teaching roles.
    - 1971-1973
      - A-Mc, 14 folders (Box 69)
      - N-Z, 11 folders (Box 70)
    - 1973-1975
      - A-G, 7 folders (Box 70)
      - H-Z, 18 folders (Box 71)
    - Pre-deanship Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 72)
      - Student Applicants, 1966-1971; 6 folders (Box 72)
      - General Correspondence, 1965-1971; 20 folders (Box 72)
    - Deanship Correspondence, 1972-1978
      - Admission Letters, 1972-1974 (Box 72)
      - General Correspondence, 1974-1979; 6 folders (Box 72)
    - Faculty Correspondence
      - Bishop, William, 1969-1977 (Box 82)
        [ER RESTRICTED until Jan. 1, 2020 ]
      - Burt, Robert, 1967-1973 (Box 82)
      - Carrington, Paul, 1963-1976 (Box 82)
      - Chambers, David, 1969-1977 (Box 82)
      - Choate, Robert, 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - Conard, Alfred, 1971-1978 (Box 82)
      - Edwards, Harry T., 1971-1976 (Box 82)
      - Estep, Samuel, 1971-1976 (Box 82)
      - Gray, Whitmore, 1971-1975 (Box 82)
      - Green, Thomas A., 1973-1977 (Box 82)
      - Harris, Robert, 1973 (Box 82)
      - Hawkins, Carl, 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - Israel, Jerold, 971-1976 (Box 82)
      - Jackson, John, 1972-1977 (Box 82)
      - Kahn, Douglas, 1971-1977 (Box 82)
      - Kalo, Joseph, 1971 (Box 82)
      - Kamisar, Yale, 1971-1978 (Box 82)
      - Kauper, Paul, 1972-1974 (Box 82)
      - Kauper, Thomas, 1971-1975 (Box 82)
      - Kennedy, Frank, 1972-1977 (Box 82)
      - Lempert, Richard, 1972-1978 (Box 82)
      - Martin, James, 1972-1978 (Box 82)
      - Miller, Arthur, 1964-1971 (Box 82)
      - Nordby, Virginia, 1971-1974 (Box 82)
      - Palmer, George, 1972-1974 (Box 82)
      - Payton, Sallyanne, 1976 (Box 82)
      - Pepe, Steven D., 1976-1977 (Box 82)
      - Pierce, William, 1971 (Box 82)
      - Plant, Marcus, 1972-1974 (Box 82)
      - Polasky, Alan, 1973-1976 (Box 82)
      - Pooley, Beverley, 1971-1977 (Box 82)
      - Proffitt, Roy, 1971-1974 (Box 82)
      - Reed, John, 1971-1976 (Box 82)
      - Regan, Donald, 1971-1977 (Box 82)
      - Rosberg, Gerald M., 1974-1975 (Box 82)
      - St. Antoine, Theodore, 1972-1978 (Box 82)
      - Sandalow, Terrance, 1973-1978 (Box 82)
      - Sax, Joseph, 1971-1978 (Box 82)
      - Siegel, Stanley, 1965-1973 (Box 82)
      - Smith, Allan F., 1974-1976 (Box 82)
      - Smith, Russel A., 1971-1974 (Box 82)
      - Soper, Philip, 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - Stein, Eric, 1971-1976 (Box 82)
      - Steiner, Peter, 1972-1977 (Box 82)
      - Vining, Joseph, 1971-1977 (Box 82)
      - Waggoner, Lawrence W., 1975 (Box 82)
      - Waterson, Jane, 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - Watson, Andrew, 1972-1978 (Box 82)
      - Wellman, Richard, 1971-1973 (Box 82)
      - Westen, Peter, 1973-1976 (Box 82)
      - White, James J., 1971-1978 (Box 82)
      - Wright, L. Hart, 1971-1975 (Box 82)
    - Topical Correspondence (as Dean-designate, Summer 1971)
      - Admissions (Box 83)
      - Alumni (Box 83)
      - American Association of University Professors (Box 83)
      - Budget (Box 83)
      - Congratulation Letters (Box 83)
      - Curriculum (Box 83)
      - CLEPR (Box 83)
      - Library (Box 83)
      - Personnel (Box 83)
      - Practicing Bar (Box 83)
      - Special Admissions (Box 83)
      - Wolfson (Box 83)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971-1978
      - A, 1975-1978 (Box 83)
      - B, 1975-1978 (Box 83)
      - Betts, Helen, 1976-1978 (Box 83)
      - C, 1975-1978 (Box 83)
      - Cohen, Donald, 1976-1978 (Box 83)
      - D, 1975-1978 (Box 83)
      - E, 1975-1978 (Box 83)
      - Ecklund, Susan, 1976-1978 (Box 83)
      - F, 1975-1978 (Box 83)
      - G, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - Gribble, James, 1971-1978 (Box 84)
      - H, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - I, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - J, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - K, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - L, 1977-1978 (Box 84)
      - Mc, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - M, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - Martindale, Roger, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - N, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - O, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - P & Q, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - Pierce, William, 1971-1978 (Box 84)
      - Proffitt, Roy, 1973-1978 (Box 84)
      - R, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - S, 1975-1978 (Box 84)
      - T, 1975-1978 (Box 85)
      - U & V, 1975-1978 (Box 85)
      - W, 1975-1978 (Box 85)
      - X, Y & Z, 1975-1978 (Box 85)
  - Terrance Sandalow
    The Terrence Sandalow subseries consist of a single alphabetically arranged correspondence file.
    - General Correspondence, 1980-1994
      - A-C, 3 folders (Box 85)
      - D-O, 12 folders (Box 85)
      - Ponek, Lisa, 1992 (Box 86)
        (includes "Seasons of the University of Michigan Law Quadrangle," 1992)
      - P-S, 3 folders (Box 86)
      - Shibuya, Mitsuko, 1984-1986 (Box 86)
      - T-W, 3 folders (Box 86)
      - Weil, Stephen, 1988-1994 (Box 86)
      - X, Y & Z, 1 folders (Box 86)
  - Lee Bollinger
    The Lee Bollinger subseries contains correspondence covering his tenure, 1987 through 1994. The correspondence is arranged in three separate files: alphabetical, chronological, and topical. Highlights of Bollinger's correspondence include thousands of hand-written notes--in an age of electronic mail--and anecdotal documentation of a couple of interesting controversies, including the hiring of feminist legal theorist Catherine McKinnon, and the accusation of the Law School's censorship of an exhibit about pornography called "Porn'im'ag'ery."
    - Correspondence--Alphabetical File, 1987-1988
      - B-D, 3 folders (Box 86)
      - F-H, 3 folders (Box 86)
      - J-P, 7 folders (Box 86)
      - R-T, 3 folders (Box 86)
      - V-W, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Correspondence--Chronological File, 1980-1994
      - 1980-July 1987 (scattered) (Box 86)
      - August-December, 1987 (Box 86)
      - January-February 1988 (Box 86)
      - March-May 1988 (Box 86)
      - June-August 1988 (Box 86)
      - September-November 1988 (Box 87)
      - December 1988 (Box 87)
      - January 1989 (Box 87)
      - February-March 1989 (Box 87)
      - April 1989 (Box 87)
      - May 1989 (Box 87)
      - June 1989 (Box 87)
      - July 1989 (Box 87)
      - August 1989 (Box 87)
      - September 1989 (Box 87)
      - October 1989 (Box 87)
      - November 1989 (Box 87)
      - December 1989 (Box 87)
      - January 1990 (Box 87)
      - February 1990 (Box 87)
      - March 1990 (Box 87)
      - April 1990 (Box 87)
      - May 1990 (Box 87)
      - June-July 1990 (Box 87)
      - August-September 1990 (Box 87)
      - October 1990 (Box 87)
      - November 1990 (Box 88)
      - December 1990 (Box 88)
      - January 1991 (Box 88)
      - February 1991 (Box 88)
      - March 1991 (Box 88)
      - April 1991 (Box 88)
      - May 1991 (Box 88)
      - June 1991 (Box 88)
      - July-August 1991 (Box 88)
      - September 1991 (Box 88)
      - October 1991 (Box 88)
      - November-December 1991 (Box 88)
      - January-February 1992 (Box 88)
      - March 1992 (Box 88)
      - April 1992 (Box 88)
      - May 1992 (Box 88)
      - June-July 1992 (Box 88)
      - August 1992 (Box 88)
      - September 1992 (Box 88)
      - October 1992 (Box 88)
      - November 1992 (Box 88)
      - December 1992 (Box 88)
      - January 1993 (Box 88)
      - February 1993 (Box 88)
      - March 1993, 2 folders (Box 89)
      - April 1993 (Box 89)
      - May 1993 (Box 89)
      - June 1993 (Box 89)
      - July 1993 (Box 89)
      - August 1993 (Box 89)
      - September 1993 (Box 89)
      - October 1993 (Box 89)
      - November 1993 (Box 89)
      - December 1993 (Box 89)
      - January 1994 (Box 89)
      - February 1994 (Box 89)
      - March 1994 (Box 89)
      - April 1994 (Box 89)
      - May 1994 (Box 89)
      - June 1994 (Box 89)
    - Correspondence--Topical File, 1984-1994
      - Alumni Reunion in Florence, 1994 (Box 90)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1992-1993 (Box 90)
      - Bankruptcy Court Committee, 1993 (Box 90)
      - Black Law Students Alliance, 1982-1985 (Box 90)
      - Clinics/Clinicians, 1993 (Box 90)
      - Cosby, Bill, 1994 (Box 90)
      - Firms re: Merit Scholarship, 1985-1987 (Box 90)
      - Fun Run, 1991 (Box 90)
      - Gay and Lesbian Issues, 1984-1993 (Box 90)
      - Higginbotham, Judge Leon, 1991-1992 (Box 90)
      - Japan Trip, 1991-1992 (Box 90)
      - Japanese Alumni, 1990-1991 (Box 90)
      - Law School Fund Computer Project, 1986-1987 (Box 90)
      - Legal Assistance for Urban Communities (LAUC), 1992-1994 (Box 90)
      - Matthiessen, Peter, 1990-1991 (Box 90)
      - "Porn'im'ag'ery" Controversy
        - Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 90)
        - 1992-1994, 4 folders (Box 90)
      - Raz, Joseph, 1993 (Box 90)
      - Saarbrucken, 1987-1988 (Box 90)
      - Sidley and Austin, 1994 (Box 90)
      - Strike, 1989 (Box 90)
      - Student Computer Room, 1992 (Box 90)
      - Student Legal Services, 1993-1994 (Box 90)
      - Summer Program Evaluation Report, 1993 (Box 90)
      - Teaching Loads Study, 1987-1991 (Box 90)
      - Tuition Revenues Returned to Law School General Fund, 1993 (Box 90)
      - Umbrella Organizations, 1986-1987 (Box 90)
      - University of Texas Lawsuit, 1992-1994 (Box 90)
      - Welch, Melanie, 1993 (Box 90)
  - Administrators
    The series Administrators is organized by name of administrator; those represented are mostly assistant or associate deans. One file, Assistant Dean--Admissions, contains material from several administrators who held this post, and is organized topically. The period represented here, 1954 to 1979, covers the advent of, and subsequent controversy over, affirmative action, also found in the records under "special admissions." Other files which are arranged topically are those of James J. Gribble, Henrietta Slote, and James J. White. The files of other administrators consist of single folders.
    - Assistant Dean--Admissions
      (Roy L. Steinheimer, Jr., ca. 1957-1968 Matthew P. McCauley, 1968-1972 Jane Waterson, 1972-1974 Roger Martindale, 1975-1979)
      - Adjustment Factors (Thomas J. Hindelang), 1967-1973 (Box 91)
      - American Indians, 1970 (Box 91)
      - Applications, 1968-1969 (Box 91)
        (includes "Some Common Questions")
      - Battles, Ronald M., 1971 (Box 91)
      - Black Law Students Alliance (Recruiting), 1968-1975 (Box 91)
      - Black Student Enrollment, 1968-1969 (Box 91)
      - Chicano Students, 1971 (Box 91)
      - Council on Legal Educational Opportunity (CLEO)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 91)
        - Detroit, 1968-1969 (Box 91)
        - Faculty Evaluations of CLEO Students, circa 1968 (Box 119)
          [SR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2043 ]
      - Combined J.D.-M.B.A. Program, 1969 (Box 91)
      - Enrollment, 1970-1979; 8 folders (Box 91)
      - Interviewing (Alumni), 1977-1978 (Box 91)
      - Legal Aid Society, 1969-1974 (Box 91)
      - Martindale, Roger, 1975-1979 (Box 91)
      - McCauley, Matthew P., 1968-1972; 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Memoranda Regarding Admissions, 1954-1961 (Box 91)
      - Mexican-American Enrollment, 1971-1975 (Box 91)
      - Michigan Daily, 1969-1972 (Box 91)
      - Minority Admissions Programs Elsewhere, 1967-1969 (Box 91)
      - Minority Groups, 1969-1974 (Box 91)
      - Minority Recruiting, 1969-1971 (Box 91)
      - Motivation Test, 1960-1971 (Box 91)
      - Negro College Recruitment Contacts, 1967-1968 (Box 91)
      - Negro Recruiting, 1967-1969 (Box 91)
      - Polasky, Alan N., 1972-1973 (Box 91)
      - Recruiting, 1969 (Box 91)
      - Regents, Vice Presidents, Etc., 1971-1972 (Box 91)
      - Scholarship, 1958-1970; 3 folders (Box 91)
      - Scholarship Committee, 1970-1977 (Box 91)
      - Sex Discrimination, 1970-1971 (Box 91)
      - Smith, Allan F., 1972-1974 (Box 119)
        [SR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2049 ]
      - Special Admissions Policy Committee--Form Letters, 1968-1969 (Box 91)
      - Standard Recommendation Form, 1969 (Box 91)
      - Study of Criteria Used in Admission of Applicants to Law School, by Roy L. Steinheimer, Jr., 1960 (Box 91)
      - Toledo Conference, 1970 (Box 91)
      - Waterson, Jane M., 1972-1974 (Box 91)
      - Working Overseas, 1969 (Box 91)
    - Battles, Ronald (Assistant to the Dean--Financial Aid)
      - 1969-1972 (Box 91)
    - Borgsdorf, Charles W. (Assistant Dean--Graduate Studies)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 91)
    - Eklund, Susan (Associate Dean)
      - 1978-1987 (Box 91)
    - Gordon, Virginia
      - 1982 (Box 91)
    - Gribble, James J. (Assistant to the Dean)
      - Cost Information--Facilities, 1971-1976 (Box 92)
      - Faculty Position Openings--Advertisements, 1972-1977 (Box 92)
      - Projects, 1965-1972 (Box 92)
    - Julin, Joseph R. (Associate Dean)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 92)
    - Kuklin, Bailey H. (Assistant Dean)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 92)
    - Lowe, Jonathon D. (Director of Law School Relations)
      - 1984 (Box 92)
    - Pierce, William J. (Associate Dean)
      - Black Law Students Alliance, 1972-1977 (Box 92)
    - Proffitt, Roy F. (Associate Dean)
      - 1969, 1978-1983; 2 folders (Box 92)
    - Rivera, Rhonda (Assistant Dean)
      - 1974-1976 (Box 92)
    - Stillwagon, Allan T. (Assistant Dean)
      - 1979-1987 (Box 92)
    - Slote, Henrietta (Administrative Manager)
      - 1979-1986 (Box 92)
      - Administrative Action Coordinators, 1982-1983 (Box 92)
      - Law School Fund Position, 1983-1984 (Box 119)
      - Minority Utilization Analysis, 1978-1984 (Box 92)
      - Postings, 1978-1985 (Box 119)
      - Professional and Administrative Evaluations, 1978; 1980 (Box 119)
      - Task Force on Minority Concerns, 1980 (Box 92)
    - White, James J. (Associate Dean)
      - Clinical Law Program, 1977-1980; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Law Review--Academic Credit Proposal, 1978 (Box 92)
      - Named Professorships, 1980 (Box 92)
  - Committees
    Committees contains the deans' files of various ad hoc and standing Law School committees, arranged alphabetically. The researcher may want to note, in particular, that the annual reports, budget proposals and correspondence of the Cook Trust are contained in the Research Committee (formerly called Graduate Research Committee, and Graduate and Research Committee) materials. Earlier Cook Trust files are located in other accessions. An earlier run of committee records is found in Boxes 50-52.
    - Academic Credit for Extracurricular Activity (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1979 (Box 93)
    - Academic Regulations Committee (Ad Hoc Law School)
      - Part One: Proposed Revision in the Grading System, circa 1966 (Box 93)
      - Part Two: Elections to the Order of the Coif, circa 1966 (Box 93)
      - Part Three: Eligibility to Continue in the School, circa 1966 (Box 93)
    - Academic Standards, 1970-1993 (Box 93)
    - Administrative Committee
      - 1969-1971 (Box 119)
      - 1971-1992 (Box 93)
      - Memoranda, 1958-1976 (Box 93)
    - Admissions
      - Admissions Policy Committee, 1971-1992; 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Special Admissions Committee, 1955-1972; 2 folders (Box 93)
    - Alumni Relations Committee, 1990 (Box 93)
    - American Journal of Comparative Law (Special Committee on), 1967 (Box 93)
    - Art and Memorials Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 93)
    - Assignments, 1955-1977 (Box 93)
    - Awards Committee, 1978; 1982 (Box 93)
    - Budget Priorities Committee, 1988 (Box 93)
    - Campbell and Miscellaneous Competitions Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 93)
    - Capital Improvements (Advisory Committee on), 1976-1990; 3 folders (Box 93)
    - Case Club (Faculty Committee), 1967 (Box 93)
    - Class Rank Committee, 1966 (Box 93)
    - Clinical Programs Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 93)
    - Clinic Search Committee, 1984-1993 (Box 93)
    - Comparative Criminal Law (Committee on), 1967 (Box 93)
    - Curriculum Committee
      - 1951-1970, undated; 4 folders (Box 93)
      - 1971-1991, 6 folders (Box 94)
    - Curriculum Study Group Committee, 1978-1992 (Box 94)
    - Dean Search Committee
      - 1965 (Box 94)
      - 1970 (Box 94)
    - Disciplinary Procedures, etc. (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1977-1980 (Box 94)
    - Faculty-Student Liaison Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 94)
    - Grading Standards and Graduation Requirements (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1968 (Box 94)
    - Graduate and Research Committee (formerly Graduate Research Committee)
      - 1969-1974 (Box 94)
      - "Legal Research at Michigan: A Report of the Graduate and Research Committee to the Law Faculty" (original and revised), 1965 (Box 94)
    - Graduate Research Committee, 1954-1969 (Box 94)
      (later Graduate and Research Committee)
    - Graduate Studies Committee, 1971-1986 (Box 94)
    - Humphrey Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 94)
    - International and Comparative Programs Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 94)
    - Library Advisory Committee, 1973-1993 (Box 94)
    - Michigan Law Critique, 1973 (Box 94)
    - Minorities (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1988-1990 (Box 94)
    - Minority Support Services (Ad Hoc Committee to Review), 1981 (Box 94)
    - Personnel Committee
      - 1971 (Box 94)
      - 1979-1994, 2 folders (Box 94)
        (includes Memorandum on the Recruitment and Hiring of Latino Faculty: Delivered to the University of Michigan Law School Personnel Committee on February 6, 1991 by the Hispanic Law Students Association)
      - Student Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 94)
    - Placement Committee, 1987 (Box 94)
    - Placement Committee (Ad Hoc), 1983-1993 (Box 94)
    - Planning Committee, 1957-1971 (Box 95)
      (Reports regarding space, size, rehabilitation, etc.)
    - Professional Responsibility Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 95)
    - Research Committee
      (formerly Graduate and Research Committee--see above)
      - Cook Trust Annual Reports
        - 1964-1981, 2 folders (Box 95)
        - 1981-1992 (Box 95)
      - Cook Trust Budget Proposals, 1965-1988; 2 folders (Box 95)
      - General Restatement of Faculty Policies regarding Research Support from Cook Funds, 1975; 1977 (Box 95)
      - Harkness Property--Rye, New York (Cook Trust), 1973 (Box 95)
      - Miscellaneous, 1964-1992; 5 folders (Box 95)
    - Scheduling (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1966 (Box 95)
    - Scholarship Committee
      - 1960-1969 (Box 95)
      - 1971 (Box 95)
      - Reports, 1970-1978 (Box 95)
    - Scholarship Awards Committee, 1971-1992 (Box 95)
    - Speakers (Ad Hoc Committee on Getting Admirable), 1966 (Box 95)
    - Special Student Programs Committee, 1968; 1971 (Box 95)
    - Student-Faculty Relations (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1969 (Box 95)
    - Student Participation on Committees/Faculty Meetings (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1969-1989; 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Summer School Special Committee, 1978-1990 (Box 96)
    - Teaching Loads Committee, 1988 (Box 96)
    - Tenure and Appointments Procedure Committee (Ad Hoc), 1972 (Box 96)
    - Tenure Committee, 1989-1993 (Box 119)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2023 ]
    - Tenure Procedure and Policies (Ad Hoc Committee on), 1987-1993 (Box 96)
    - Visitor's Committee (1973-1992) (Box 96)
    - Wolfson Trust Committee, 1963-1995; 2 folders (Box 96)
  - Programs and Projects
    The Programs and Projects series contains records from four Law School programs: the Child Advocacy Legal Clinic (CALC), the Institute of Continuing Legal Education (ICLE), Legal Assistance for Urban Communities (LAUC), and the Minority Affairs Program (MAP--formerly MAAP, Minority Academic Advancement Program).
    - Child Advocacy Legal Clinic (CALC)
      The CALC files contain a small amount of correspondence and memoranda, and student evaluations of the clinic from 1976 through 1989.
      - 1976-1984 (Box 96)
      - Don Duquete--Ethics Opinion, 1983-1984 (Box 96)
      - Evaluations
        - Fall 1976-Summer 1985, 24 folders (Box 96)
        - Fall 1985-Fall 1989, 12 folders (Box 97)
    - Institute of Continuing Legal Education (ICLE)
      - 1962-1974, 8 folders (Box 97)
        (includes Executive Committee meeting agendas, exhibits and annual reports)
      - 1975-1992, 5 folders (Box 98)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1980; 3 folders (Box 98)
      - Director Search, 1973 (Box 119)
      - Labor Arbitrator Development Program, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Legal Assistance for Urban Communities (LAUC)